What's up, man?
How you doing, Will?
Man, it's all love.
Great to meet you.
How you feeling, brother?
Great, man. Happy to be out here.
Okay, okay, we got the color vibe.
Who am I here with today?
Will Smith in the building.
Did you come from a lot of money?
No, no. I came from the opposite.
So what was your turning point to financial freedom?
I realized that taking advice from somebody who hasn't
done what you want to do is almost insanity.
Like, listening to people who haven't done the thing
that you want to do, that makes you crazy.
Do you think money buys happiness?
Hell no.
There's an amount of money that
once you pass it, it buys misery.
So what was the most amount of
money you made in a single year?
In a single year.
Guys, I'm about to interview the
legendary Will Smith out in Los Angeles.
From the Fresh Prince of Bel-Air to the
Box Office King, Will Smith has done it all.
And he's become one of the greatest entertainers, one of the greatest
actors of not just my generation, but of all time, you guys.
So this interview is about to
be one of the best we've done.
So make sure you stay tuned from start to finish.
With that being said, let's go meet Will
and go see what he has to say.
All right, you guys.
So we just got in the gate
of where we're going to be interviewing Will.
He's going to be coming out at any minute now.
So we're going to be linking up
with him in just a few minutes.
Come on, you guys.
What's up, man?
How you doing, Will?
It's all love.
Great to meet you.
How you feeling, brother?
Great, man.
Happy to be out.
Okay, okay.
We got the color vibes.
I'm Jack.
What's up, man?
I'm Josh.
Good to meet you.
Josh.
What's the deal?
Happy to be out here.
Man, it's all good.
You on a big run lately.
A little run right now.
A little bit of a run.
For sure.
We had a great shoot yesterday with Tom.
Tom, yeah, I saw that.
I was telling him it was like three hours.
We hit a million on IG.
So just trying to keep on going, man.
Love that.
We're excited about this, man.
We love all that you do, and we're
just happy to be here with you right now.
No, this is great.
Who am I here with today?
Will Smith in the building.
And for those that don't know, what industry
did you decide to pursue a career in?
Well, I started in music, and then I
went into television, and then into film, and ultimately
into production and business.
So you're a little diversified.
Well, you know, man, I
like to have a couple hyphens.
Do you think people should hyper-focus on
one thing when they're starting out, or do
you like the idea of kind
of diversifying your efforts into different ventures?
How do you feel about diversification?
Because you wear many hats.
I think of it like an arrow.
So if you think about the one thing you do
really well at the tip of the arrow, and you
got to do it really specifically and really
well, and then after the arrow bursts through
the universe, then all the other things
you do can come through behind it.
But I think it's really, really
important to, like, master one thing.
One of my favorite books growing up was The
Alchemist, and it says the whole of the universe
is contained in a single grain of sand.
So I took that to be...
If you learn how to do one thing really,
really well, you can expand your knowledge base from
the comprehension of that one thing.
Now, you've become one of the greatest entertainers
of all time, undoubtedly one of the greatest
of all time actors.
Thank you, brother.
Thank you, thank you.
What's been the biggest driving factor
of your success throughout your career?
If you can attribute it to one thing, or
maybe it's a couple of things, what's really led
to your success that separated you apart from
99% of people in one of the most competitive
industries?
One of the things I discovered really early is
that the wind goes to the most hours committed.
When I realized...
I realized that how I spent my time and attention
on a daily basis, if I do something for 10
hours a day, and you only do it for 9
hours a day, in a year, it's going to be really
hard for you to beat me.
So I realized very, very early, I was probably
18 by the time I knew that the time applied
was cumulative, and even if you were more talented
than me, if I put in more hours than
you, it would be really
hard for you to beat me.
Now, you've played many roles in the entertainment business.
As an actor, what's the most interesting
thing that you've learned about people throughout
your career?
I guess one of the big things that I've
learned is that even what we call people, what you
say a person, is not actually a person.
It's like a personality.
It's a small constellation of ideas that a
person has chosen to live within and say that
that's us.
And I guess the thing I've learned is
that we're way bigger than we think we are.
We're way bigger than we allow ourselves to be.
We are way more than the little sliver
of race, creed, color, city, country, you know,
that we confine ourselves to.
And that idea of a person can even
become the prison that keeps us from excelling.
Now, you starred in the movie The Pursuit of Happiness.
It's one of the most perspective-shaping movies of all time.
Yeah, for sure.
Did that change your perspective when you were filming it?
One of the big things that I learned
from Chris Gardner and working on that movie is
that suffering is...
is a gift.
The universe teaches through difficulty.
God teaches through suffering and hard times.
And the shaping of a person, the shaping
of a willpower, the shaping of your energy is
almost always exclusively in adversity.
And with Chris Gardner, how he talked about
the education of his suffering was one of
the major lessons that I took away from that movie.
Like...
to get comfortable being uncomfortable
if you want to achieve.
Do you believe in God?
Absolutely.
How important has faith been for you throughout your career?
The idea of God and people throw
different words around and people have different definitions.
I believe in an energy that is constantly
creating in all things that if I cultivate
a relationship with, I can
be more powerful than I am.
I can do things a hundredfold what will could do.
If I tap into the movement and the
energy and the flow and the creative intelligence
that's making the sun and the
stars and the trees that we're breathing.
If I tap into that, I know I can be
infinitely more powerful, creative than me with my ego construct.
Another movie you starred in is Hitch.
I think one of the greatest lessons of that,
there's a quote that the world is overly cruel
to shy men and it rewards the courageous.
Mmm.
Confidence and belief in oneself is one
of the biggest things people that struggle with
and it's what prevents them from finding success.
How did you personally find the self belief
and the confidence within to go out and make
tens, hundreds of millions of dollars
and be so successful in your industry?
I think one of the biggest things I
learned about confidence was on the Fresh Prince of
Bel Air.
The confidence is one side of it, but
it's built on not being scared to look stupid.
So it looks like confidence when
you're not scared to fail, right?
It's not actually confidence.
It's confidence in its seeds.
It becomes confidence after you get used to
rejection, you get used to doing it wrong,
you get used to being okay when you tell
a joke and that one's not funny and you get
comfortable if you hit three out of ten,
you know, you're in the hall of fame.
The comfort to fail in front of
people is what is perceived as confidence.
You stop worrying about what everybody else thinks.
Taking advice from somebody who hasn't done
what you want to do is almost insanity.
Like.
You know, you're talking to people who haven't done
the thing that you want to do and ingesting
the poison of their ignorant opinion.
That makes you crazy.
It reminds me of the saying, never take
advice from someone you wouldn't trade places with.
Right.
Yes, exactly.
And it was one, you know, I got that
one time I was going through something and I called
Quincy Jones and you know, I
don't even remember what the problem was.
And I asked him and Quincy was like, he said,
man, how the fuck I'm going to give you advice.
It was a little bit of a.
It was like he said, I wouldn't
have chose none of the shit you chose.
He said, whatever, whatever you're
doing, just keep doing that.
And it was like that was a real vote
of confidence that even somebody in his position backed
off of giving advice in the understanding
that everybody knows what they know and only
they can know for them.
Nobody can really know for you.
And you know, you'll actually get to a point
where you ask for advice less and you just
sort of watch and listen.
And then let people tell you
what they think from their behavior.
Yeah.
And you kind of lean on your own intuition.
Yes, absolutely.
One time somebody told me that if a bird
lands on a branch, does the bird trust the branch
or does it trust its wings?
I've seen many birds land on branches, but
what I've never seen is the branch break and
the bird fall and die.
Yeah.
So guys, listen very carefully because I'm about
to drop one of the most insane offers
that I've ever done for the next 24 hours only.
So exactly one year ago today, I launched
what has now become the number one community
for entrepreneurs in the entire world.
And it's called the school of mentors.
And inside the school of mentor, I give
you direct access to the hundreds of millionaires
and billionaires that I interview and give
you the opportunity to ask them questions
live.
And now in order to celebrate our one
year anniversary, we are going to be doing something
insane.
We are giving you the opportunity to
join the greatest entrepreneur community on the
planet for just $1 a day.
Guys, you can literally speak with millionaires
and billionaires every single week and ask
them questions live for just one freaking dollar a day.
Let me be clear.
This isn't a course.
This isn't a mastermind that costs you $25,000.
This isn't outdated information.
This is live access to the people that
have already built what you're trying to build.
So if you're in a nine to five and
you want to change your life, this is for you.
If you have a business idea and you want
to bring it to life, this is for you.
And if you're already an entrepreneur and you
want to scale to seven, eight, and even
nine figures, this is for you.
But here's the thing.
The only catch is that this offer is only
good for 24 hours after that, it's gone and
we're raising the price again.
Let me just make a quick note.
I'm not going to go
into too much detail on this.
I'm just going to share some tips and tricks
and tips and tricks that you can use to get
your business going.
you want to bring it to life, this is
for you. And if you're already an entrepreneur and you
want to scale to seven, eight, and even nine
figures, this is for you. But here's the thing.
The only catch is that this offer is only
good for 24 hours. After that, it's gone and we're
raising the price again. So if you're watching this
right now, you still have time. All you have
to do is go down and click the link
in the description of this video to join the School
of Mentors, the number one community for business owners
in the entire world. I can't wait to see
you on the inside of the community. But with
that being said, let's get back to the interview
with Will. What is the greatest piece of
advice that Will Smith has ever received? There's one
lesson that a mentor taught you throughout
your career, right? You've networked with billionaires,
you've networked with the most successful people
across different industries. Give me one piece
of advice you could give to somebody who may
not have a great mentor. That's good. There's a couple
of them. My grandmother, when we were going on tour,
as we were getting on the tour bus and she
were going away, she said, hey baby, just remember
everywhere you go, one day you're going to have to
go back. I didn't get it in that moment.
But as I started to go in my career,
I started to realize like, oh shit, it's all relationships.
Everything is relationships. You never know. You
meet somebody right now and they're 16,
but when they're 24, they're going to
be running the company that you're trying to
sell something to. And when they're 34, your kids
go to their kid's school and all of that,
and it's like you start to
develop a network of friends throughout,
and you absolutely never know. We have no clue
how we're going to cross paths in the future.
And it's critical that even as small as a
smile in a moment, you recognize that every person is
going to be a part of the tapestry of your
future. And just taking a minute to connect and to realize
that what you're going to build, there's going to
be a necessity for hundreds, if not thousands of
other people to help you. People will take you places,
that money can't.
Amen.
So did you come from a lot of money?
No, no. I came from the opposite.
So what was your turning point to financial
freedom? Give me that turning point in your life.
I realized that sometimes what you're good at
is different than what you like. So I love
making music. I love being on stage, but I'm
actually better as an actor. And I had to make
the choice to go with what I was
better at. And I tried to mix the...
Mix the music in there. But the real turning point
for me was realizing that my greatest skill set was
acting. And I chose to master that above all
things in my career. And then finance came behind that,
behind the mastery.
So what was the most amount of
money you made in a single year?
Oh, I don't like to talk about that.
Maybe revenue across all the businesses?
Yeah, yeah. There was plenty of zeros, plenty of
zeros, but I don't like to discuss the actual
amount.
Maybe an accomplishment financially.
Even from like a box office
standpoint that you're the most proud of?
Hancock and I Am Legend were within six months
of each other. That was one of the biggest years
of my career and one of the most creative
periods. I think Hancock was in June and then
I Am Legend was in
December. Christmas was nice that year.
Right. Do you think money buys happiness?
Hell no. Actually, there's an amount of money that
once you pass it, it buys misery. Once you
have a certain amount of money, you're going to
have a lot of money. And I think that's
the most important thing.
I think that's the most important thing.
The most important thing is that you're going to
have a lot of money. And if you have a
certain amount of money, you can change people's
lives. So it's really all people can think
about. So it's difficult to make new
friendships at certain financial points, right? In America,
somewhere around a million dollars a year, it
starts going the other way where it's more
problems beyond that. And you start
getting into really an attack zone.
You broke this down beautifully
about clifftop versus rock bottom.
Yeah, for sure.
Everybody thinks when you hit
rock bottom, that's when you change.
Yeah, for sure.
Everybody thinks when you hit rock bottom,
that's when you change. Can you break that
down real quick for them?
The idea of clifftop, it's like a corresponding
place to rock bottom. And after you've had
all the money you've wanted and you've had
all the sex you've wanted and you've created
all the things and all the fame,
there's a corresponding abyss that you can actually
pop off of the top of the material
world. And you're like, oh shit, there's literally
nothing I want to buy. There's literally nobody
that I want to have new sex with. There's
nothing.
And it's a terrifying place when you
realize nothing material can actually satisfy you.
And it's a similar abyss at rock bottom.
And the realization is that what you're actually
looking for is you. What you're actually looking
for is a comfort that will only come with
you totally by yourself with none of this
shit. And then once you are stable in your
place, you were talking about the bird and
the branch. Once you're stable in your place,
you were talking about the bird and the
branch. Once you're stable, you're going to be able
to get out of this shit. You're going to have
a lot of fun, but you're not going to be able
to get out of this shit.
Once you're comfortable in your wings, the branch
can be weak or strong. When you get
a strong branch is great. When you get
a weak branch, that's cool. It's another lesson.
You'll find another one. But there's a
certain stability in yourself that you trust yourself
that you can handle whatever comes that is
above any kind of false material safety comfort.
Because it's not real. There are diseases
that are not curable that your money won't
be able to fix. There are relationships
that break up that you can't buy.
You're going T쟁 is back. When loved ones
die, there's nothing you can do. So there's
certain things in this life that only an
absolute steadiness in yourself in the face of whatever
life has to offer. That's the only
thing that can make this place bare.
Your last message to the younger generation
in one sentence.
Recognize the absolute infinite nature of
what you could do. Consciousness is this crazy
gift that literally can do anything. You don't
just need a friend. You need a family.
So should you sits with a girlfriend, what's
You don't have to go to
the job you went to today.
You don't have to live where you live now.
You don't have to be
in the relationship that you're in.
You literally can do anything that you choose.
It just takes a certain amount of willingness to suffer.
But this thing, whatever we are, is
the crazy, infinite, magical tool of creation.
Will, you got amazing advice, my friend.
Appreciate you, brother.
Thank you so much for your time.
I appreciate you.
That was great.
Guys, we just wrapped up an interview with Will Smith.
That's one of my favorite
interviews I've ever done, you guys.
He just gave so much incredible advice for
people trying to break into any industry, man.
The life advice there.
Him talking about not taking advice
from people you wouldn't trade places with.
And the bigger you get, the less
you have to listen to other people.
But guys, like and subscribe for Amazing Condom.
We've got coming every single week, guys.
I'm bringing you guys the
most successful, the wealthiest people,
the biggest people in every industry directly to you
to give you guys the advice
on how to change your lives,
become the best version of yourselves,
and create financial freedom and build generational wealth.
Great interview out here in Los Angeles.
And one more thing, guys.
Go down and click the link
down in the description of this video
to join the School of Mentors,
the number one community for
business owners in the entire world
where you will get
mentorship directly from the eight-figure,
the nine-figure, and the
billionaire entrepreneurs that I interview
where you can get access to them every single week.
Guys, every week, I bring in a different mentor
to give you guys personalized one-on-one advice
and answer all your questions on how to start,
on how to scale your business, on how to sell,
how to market,
and how to grow your business.
And I'll see you in the next video.